[
  { "front": "Alabama", "back": "Montgomery" },
  { "front": "Alaska", "back": "Juneau" },
  { "front": "Arizona", "back": "Phoenix" },
  { "front": "Arkansas", "back": "Little Rock" },
  { "front": "California", "back": "Sacramento" },
  { "front": "Colorado", "back": "Denver" },
  { "front": "Connecticut", "back": "Hartford" },
  { "front": "Delaware", "back": "Dover" },
  { "front": "Florida", "back": "Tallahassee" },
  { "front": "Georgia", "back": "Atlanta" },
  { "front": "Hawaii", "back": "Honolulu" },
  { "front": "Idaho", "back": "Boise" },
  { "front": "Illinois", "back": "Springfield" },
  { "front": "Indiana", "back": "Indianapolis" },
  { "front": "Iowa", "back": "Des Moines" },
  { "front": "Kansas", "back": "Topeka" },
  { "front": "Kentucky", "back": "Frankfort" },
  { "front": "Louisiana", "back": "Baton Rouge" },
  { "front": "Maine", "back": "Augusta" },
  { "front": "Maryland", "back": "Annapolis" },
  { "front": "Massachusetts", "back": "Boston" },
  { "front": "Michigan", "back": "Lansing" },
  { "front": "Minnesota", "back": "Saint Paul" },
  { "front": "Mississippi", "back": "Jackson" },
  { "front": "Missouri", "back": "Jefferson City" },
  { "front": "Montana", "back": "Helena" },
  { "front": "Nebraska", "back": "Lincoln" },
  { "front": "Nevada", "back": "Carson City" },
  { "front": "New Hampshire", "back": "Concord" },
  { "front": "New Jersey", "back": "Trenton" },
  { "front": "New Mexico", "back": "Santa Fe" },
  { "front": "New York", "back": "Albany" },
  { "front": "North Carolina", "back": "Raleigh" },
  { "front": "North Dakota", "back": "Bismarck" },
  { "front": "Ohio", "back": "Columbus" },
  { "front": "Oklahoma", "back": "Oklahoma City" },
  { "front": "Oregon", "back": "Salem" },
  { "front": "Pennsylvania", "back": "Harrisburg" },
  { "front": "Rhode Island", "back": "Providence" },
  { "front": "South Carolina", "back": "Columbia" },
  { "front": "South Dakota", "back": "Pierre" },
  { "front": "Tennessee", "back": "Nashville" },
  { "front": "Texas", "back": "Austin" },
  { "front": "Utah", "back": "Salt Lake City" },
  { "front": "Vermont", "back": "Montpelier" },
  { "front": "Virginia", "back": "Richmond" },
  { "front": "Washington", "back": "Olympia" },
  { "front": "West Virginia", "back": "Charleston" },
  { "front": "Wisconsin", "back": "Madison" },
  { "front": "Wyoming", "back": "Cheyenne" }
]
